Inventory of the J. B. Okie papers, 1893-1921
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
J. B. Okie papers
1893-1921
Okie, J. B. (John Brognard), 1864-1930.
00123
26.75 cubic feet (61 boxes)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Biography of J. B. Okie
J.B. Okie (1864-1930) was a Wyoming sheep rancher and businessman. He came to Rawlins, Wyoming, in 1882 and worked briefly as a cowboy before buying his first herd of sheep, which he grazed along the Sweetwater River before moving them to the Badwater Creek in Fremont County, Wyoming, in 1883. In 1884 he built his first home on the Badwater at Lost Cabin, Wyoming. He formed the Bighorn Sheep Company at Casper in 1893 and moved its headquarters to Lost Cabin in 1902. Also in 1893, he bought the Smith Mercantile Company in Casper, Wyoming, and reopened it as the Casper Mercantile Company with his brother Fred as manager; this store was closed in 1898 when Fred Okie left Wyoming. The first Bighorn Sheep Company mercantile store opened in Lost Cabin in 1895, with later expansion into the central Wyoming communities of Arminto, Lysite, Kaycee, Moneta, and Shoshoni. In 1919, Okie bought the Piggly Wiggly stores franchise for Mexico, where he owned six stores.
Scope and Content
The collection is materials related to Okie's Wyoming ranch and mercantile businesses and includes 20 boxes of correspondence (1894-1921); 31 boxes of general business files, arranged alphabetically; day books of the mercantile stores (1899-1904); three letter books of the Bighorn Sheep Company (1897-1902), with some entries for the Casper Mercantile Company (1897-1898); a journal of the Buffalo Creek Company (1902-1903); a herd book for the Bighorn Sheep Company (1898-1906); a minute book for the Bighorn Sheep Company (1893-1909) and a passenger and freight record book of the No Wood and Lost Cabin Stage Line (1911-1914).
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by J. B. Okie at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
Collection material received from J.B. Okie and Family in 1966, Mrs. V.G. Okie in 1971, and Karen Love in 1972.
Access Terms
Bighorn Sheep Company.; No Wood and Lost Cabin Stage Line.; Buffalo Creek Company.; Casper Mercantile Company.; Sheep industry -- Wyoming -- Fremont County.; General stores -- Wyoming -- Lost Cabin.; General stores -- Wyoming -- Casper.; General stores -- Wyoming -- Fremont County.; General stores -- Wyoming -- Natrona County.; Sheep ranches -- Wyoming -- Fremont County.; Coaching (Transportation) -- Wyoming.; Lost Cabin (Wyo.); Fremont County (Wyo.); Wyoming -- History -- 1890-1918.; Wyoming -- History -- 1919-1945.; Daybooks.; Journals (bookkeeping records); Minute books.; Letter books.; Businessmen.; Sheep ranchers.
Agriculture and Natural Resources; Ranching; Business, Industry, Labor, and Commerce; Retail Trade; Transportation; Social Life and Customs; Wyoming
Container List
- Series I. Letter and Minute Books
  - Letter Books
    - No Wood & Lost Cabin Stage Line Record Book, 1897-1898 (Box 60)
    - No Wood & Lost Cabin Stage Line Record Book, 1900-1901 (Box 60)
    - No Wood & Lost Cabin Stage Line Record Book, 1901-1902 (Box 61)
  - Minutes Books - BHS Co, Day Books
    - 1897 August (Box 52)
    - 1898-1899 (Box 52)
    - 1898-1899 (Box 52)
    - 1899-1900 (Box 53)
    - 1899-1900 (Box 53)
    - 1899-1900 (Box 57)
    - 1900 January 29-May 7 (Box 53)
    - 1900 May 7-September 10 (Box 54)
    - 1900 August 11-December 2 (Box 54)
    - 1900 September 11-December 12 (Box 54)
    - 1900-1901 (Box 55)
    - 1901 April 2-May 30 (Box 55)
    - 1901 September 9-December 10 (Box 55)
    - 1901-1902 (Box 56)
    - 1902 April-June (Box 56)
    - 1902 June-October (Box 56)
    - 1902 June-September (Box 56)
    - 1902 July-November (Box 56)
    - 1903-1904 (Box 58)
    - Sheep, Cattle, Horses, undated (Box 59)
- Series II. General Material
  - "A" (Box 1)
  - Aberdeen Mill Co. (Box 1)
  - R. D. Adams (Box 1)
  - Adjustable Table Co. (Box 1)
  - Allen Brothers (Box 1)
  - American Book Co. (Box 1)
  - American Carbolite Co. (Box 1)
  - American Carbolite Sales Co. (Box 1)
  - American Cordial & Distilling Co. (Box 1)
  - The American Steel & Wire Co. (Box 1)
  - American Surety Co. (Box 1)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 1)
  - Arapahoe Merc. Co. (Box 1)
  - Arminto Store (Box 1)
  - Armour & Co. (Box 1)
  - Atlantic Refining Co. (Box 1)
  - Atwater Kent Mfg. Works (Box 1)
  - The Automobile Blue Book Publishing Co. (Box 1)
  - "B", 1919-1920 (Box 2)
  - Baggs Mercantile Co. (Box 2)
  - Balance Sheets (Box 2)
  - M. C. Barrow (Box 2)
  - Barteldes Seed Co. (Box 2)
  - Battle Renwick (Box 2)
  - Beatrice Creamery Co. (Box 3)
  - A. W. Bebb & Co. (Box 3)
  - Jacob Becker (Box 3)
  - Beebe & Runyan Furniture Co. (Box 3)
  - Bell Paint Co. (Box 3)
  - Bemis Bagg Co. (Box 3)
  - Bemis Omaha Bag Co. (Box 3)
  - Bighorn Milling Co. & W. R. Johnson (Box 3)
  - Bighorn Hot Springs Bottling Work (Box 3)
  - Big Horn Sheep Co. Minute Book (Box 3)
  - Blackman & Griffin Co. (Box 3)
  - John Blessing (Box 3)
  - A. Booth & Co. (Box 3)
  - Borden's Condensed Milk (Box 3)
  - S. F. Bowser & Co. (Box 3)
  - Earl C. Boyle (Box 3)
  - H. N. Boyd & Co. (Box 3)
  - Howard Boyer Wool Co. (Box 3)
  - S. A. Bristol Co. (Box 4)
  - George A. Brooks Barile Mills (Box 4)
  - J. S. Brown Merc. Co. (Box 4)
  - Watson A. Brown (Box 4)
  - Browning Bros. Co. (Box 4)
  - The Brulet & Bourk Comm. Co. (Box 4)
  - Building A/C (Box 4)
  - Burke & Riner (Box 4)
  - C. A. Burlew (Box 4)
  - Burley & Tyrell. (Box 4)
  - Burroughs Adding Machine Co. (Box 4)
  - Burton Seed Co. (Box 4)
  - Business Clearing (Box 4)
  - Fred H. Busley (Box 4)
  - Butler Bros. (Box 4)
  - "C", 1919-1920 (Box 5)
  - C. & N. W. R. R. (Box 5)
  - California Power Work (Box 5)
  - Messrs. Campbell & Reid (Box 5)
  - Cancelled Checks (Box 5)
  - Philip Carey Co. (Box 5)
  - Carpenter Paper Co. (Box 5)
  - Carson Crockery Co. (Box 6)
  - Carson Pine Scott & Co. (Box 6)
  - A. S. Carter (Box 6)
  - Casper Battling Works (Box 6)
  - Casper Commission Co. (Box 6)
  - Casper Ice Cream Co. (Box 6)
  - Casper National Bank (Box 6)
  - Casper Steam Laundry Co. (Box 6)
  - Casper Storage Co. (Box 6)
  - Central Broom Co. (Box 6)
  - Chamberlain Medicine Co. (Box 6)
  - E. T. Chapin Co. (Box 6)
  - Charge & Credit Slips (Box 6)
  - J. W. Cheever (Box 6)
  - The Cheyenne Creamery Co. (Box 6)
  - Chicago Burlington & Quincy R. R. (Box 6)
  - Chicago & North Western R. R. (Box 6)
  - Chicago Telephone Supply Co. (Box 6)
  - Cloak Drummer Co. (Box 7)
  - Cole Manufacturing Co. (Box 7)
  - The Coleman Lamp Co. (Box 7)
  - Collins Plow Co. (Box 7)
  - Colorado Fuel & Iron Co., Denver, Colo. (Box 7)
  - The Colorado Portland Cement Co. (Box 7)
  - Colorado Portland Co. (Box 7)
  - Commissioner of Public Lands, Cheyenne, Wyoming (Box 7)
  - E. A. Condax & Co. (Box 7)
  - Continental Oil Co. (Box 7)
  - Continental Supply Co. (Box 7)
  - P. B. Coolidge (Box 8)
  - William Cooper & Nephews. (Box 8)
  - Cooley-Wirth Printing Co. (Box 8)
  - N. Cotton Co. (Box 8)
  - County Clerk Fremont Co. (F. W. Thomas) (Box 8)
  - Mrs. H. O. Cox (Box 8)
  - Crawford Fruit & Produce Co. (Box 8)
  - Crawn Overal Mfg. Co. (Box 8)
  - Curtis & Co. Mfg. Co. (Box 8)
  - Danforth Mill Co. (Box 8)
  - John Deere Plow Co. (Box 8)
  - C. E. DeGroot (Box 8)
  - Delfelder. (Box 8)
  - DeLoach Mill Mfg. Co. (Box 8)
  - J. W. Denio Milling Co. (Box 8)
  - Denver Dry Goods Co. (Box 9)
  - Denver Hatch Case Co. (Box 9)
  - Denver Photo Materials Co. (Box 9)
  - Denver Post (Box 9)
  - Denver Tent & Awning Co. (Box 9)
  - Denver Watch Case Co. (Box 9)
  - John Derrig & Co. (Box 9)
  - Diels Bros. (Box 9)
  - Eugene Dietzgen Co. (Box 9)
  - Dipping a/c, 1904 May (Box 9)
  - M. A. Disbrow & Co. (Box 9)
  - W. A. Discus (Box 9)
  - Dodson, Fisher, Brockman Co. (Box 9)
  - T. A. Dougherty (Box 9)
  - Duncan Electrical Manufacturing Co. (Box 9)
  - DuPont de Nemours & Co. (Box 9)
  - Durkin, Reeves & Co. (Box 9)
  - Dutcher & Robertson (Box 9)
  - "E", 1919-1920 (Box 10)
  - E - F (Box 10)
  - East Liverpool Pottery Co. (Box 10)
  - Economy Shirt Co. (Box 10)
  - Ehrlich & Sons (Box 10)
  - Elgin System Creamery Co. (Box 10)
  - Elliott-Fisher Co. (Box 10)
  - Ellsworth & Thayer Mfg. Co. (Box 10)
  - Engle-McMichael Co. (Box 10)
  - Expense Bills (Box 10)
  - "F", 1919-1920 (Box 10)
  - Fabricius Toy & Notion Co. (Box 10)
  - Dr. Peter Fahrney (Box 10)
  - John T. Farrwell Co. (Box 10)
  - J. F. Fendrich (Box 10)
  - Ferguson-McKinney Dry Goods Co. (Box 10)
  - D. M. Ferry Co. (Box 10)
  - Fidelity-Phenix Fire Ins. Co. (Box 10)
  - Marshell Field and Co. (Box 11)
  - First National Bank (Box 11)
  - First National Bank - Shoshoni (Box 11)
  - First National Bank - Worland (Box 11)
  - B. S. Flersheim Mercantile Co. (Box 11)
  - Florence Hdw. Co. (Box 11)
  - J. A. Folger & Co. (Box 11)
  - Foot, Schulze & Co. (Box 11)
  - Ford Motor Co. (Box 11)
  - Ford Optical Co. (Box 11)
  - Fourth Asst. P.M. or Post Office General Correspondence (Box 11)
  - Freighter's Slips (Box 12)
  - Fremont County (Box 13)
  - Fry & McGill Motor Supply Co. (Box 13)
  - D. E. Fuller (Box 13)
  - "G", 1919-1920 (Box 13)
  - Gamble Robinson & Co. (Box 13)
  - Gate City Hat Co. (Box 13)
  - Gem Cutlery Co. (Box 13)
  - General Correspondence re Mail (Box 13)
  - General Merchandise - Butter & Eggs (Box 13)
  - Gerlach & Carbon (Box 13)
  - Gilinsky Fruit Co. (Box 13)
  - Gillette Sales Co. (Box 13)
  - B. F. Goodrich Co. (Box 13)
  - Gordon & Ferguson (Box 13)
  - Great Western Store Co. (Box 13)
  - W. F. Griffin. (Box 13)
  - Chas. D. Griffith Shore Co. (Box 13)
  - Guiterman Brothers (Box 13)
  - "H", 1919-1920 (Box 14)
  - Hallack & Howard Lumber Co. (Box 14)
  - Hallwood Cash Register Co. (Box 14)
  - Hammond Packing Co. (Box 14)
  - Hedges-Atkins, McGee Co., Denver (Box 14)
  - Heebner & Sons (Box 14)
  - Peter Henderson & Co. (Box 14)
  - H. Hendrich (Box 14)
  - Hess Flume Co. (Box 14)
  - Heynemann & Co. (Box 14)
  - Hibbard, Spencer, Barlett & Co. (Box 14)
  - Hides & Pelts (Box 14)
  - R. J. Hillier (Box 14)
  - The Howard-Boyer Wool Co. (Box 14)
  - Hudson Coal Co. (Box 14)
  - H. A. Hyatt (Box 14)
  - Hyatt & Darke (Box 14)
  - The Independence Coffee & Spice Co. (Box 14)
  - Indianapolis Luck Co. (Box 14)
  - Robert H. Ingersoll & Bros. (Box 14)
  - International Harvester Co. (Box 14)
  - International Harvester Co. of America (Box 14)
  - International Mfg. Co. (Box 14)
  - International Salt Co. (Box 14)
  - Interstate Rubber Co. (Box 14)
  - Interstate Salt Co. (Box 14)
  - Interstate Unemployment System (Box 14)
  - B. L. James M. & M. Co. (Box 15)
  - Jewell Bros. (Box 15)
  - Clarence T. Johnson (Box 15)
  - K-L (Box 15)
  - Kanson, A. (Box 15)
  - Keller Strauss Distilling Co. (Box 15)
  - Kelly Merc. Co. (Box 15)
  - The Kentucky Tobacco Product Co. (Box 15)
  - Julius Kessler & Co. (Box 15)
  - Wilson S. Kimball (Box 15)
  - Kimball Drug Co. (Box 15)
  - C. H. King Co. (Box 15)
  - C. H. King Co. (Box 15)
  - C. H. King Co. (Box 15)
  - Kingman Implement Co. (Box 15)
  - F. P. Kirkendall and Co. (Box 15)
  - W. H. Kistler Stationary Co. Denver (Box 15)
  - Joseph Knittel Show Case Co. (Box 15)
  - Kronantz Saddlery Co. (Box 15)
  - Lawrence-Hensley Fruit Co. (Box 16)
  - Lee, Coit, Andreesen Hdw. Co. (Box 16)
  - H. D. Lee Merchantile Co. (Box 16)
  - Lee Broom & Duster Co. (Box 16)
  - Legal Documents (Box 16)
  - Legal Documents (Box 17)
  - A. T. Lewis & Son Dry Goods Co. (Box 17)
  - Liberty Overall Co. (Box 17)
  - The Lindquist Cracker Co. (Box 17)
  - Lininger Implement Co. (Box 17)
  - Lininger and Metcalf Co. (Box 17)
  - C. B. Liver and Co. (Box 17)
  - Lo. (Box 17)
  - Loomis Machine Co. (Box 17)
  - Lost Cabin Bar Co. (Box 17)
  - Lumber & Posts (Box 17)
  - Lumber Received (Box 17)
  - Lumber Sold (Box 17)
  - Lyon Bros. (Box 17)
  - Lyon & Healy (Box 17)
  - "M", 1919-1920 (Box 18)
  - A. C. McClurg & Co. (Box 18)
  - McCord Brady Co. (Box 18)
  - McElwain - Barton Shoe Co. (Box 18)
  - S. A. McKenzie Woolrod, Wyoming (Box 18)
  - McPhee & McGinnity. (Box 19)
  - Manning - Bowman & Co. (Box 19)
  - Marke Bros. Saddlery Co. (Box 19)
  - Marks Tailoring Co. (Box 19)
  - Marquis & Co. (Box 19)
  - Marquis & Co. Wolton, Wyoming (Box 19)
  - Marshall Field And Co. (Box 19)
  - Martin - Cott Hat Co. (Box 19)
  - The Merchants Biscuit Co. (Box 19)
  - Meshawaka Woolen Mfg. Co. & Wm. Taschar (Box 19)
  - Midland Chair & Seating Co. (Box 19)
  - E. B. Millar Coffee Co. (Box 19)
  - Milwaukee Corrugating Co. (Box 19)
  - A. J. Mokler (Box 19)
  - Moneta Store Co. (Box 20)
  - Moneta Store A. R. White (Box 20)
  - Moneta Store - Sheep Shearing records., 1914-1921 (Box 20)
  - J. K. Moore Co. (Box 20)
  - J. & B. Moos (Box 20)
  - Morey Mercantile Co. (Box 20)
  - Mound City Duck & Rubber Co. (Box 21)
  - Mountian States Telephone Co. (Box 21)
  - Reed Murdoch & Co. (Box 21)
  - S. F. Myers Co. (Box 21)
  - National Bank - Cheyenne, Wyoming (Box 21)
  - National Biscuit Co. (Box 21)
  - Nebraska Moline Plow Co. (Box 21)
  - Nebraska Seed Co. (Box 21)
  - Neligh Mills Co. (Box 22)
  - W. C. Nevin Candy Co. (Box 22)
  - Noble and Bragg (Box 22)
  - Noble Land & Noble. (Box 22)
  - Northern Ohio Blanket Mills (Box 22)
  - Northeastern Warehouse Co. (Box 22)
  - Northwastern Comp. - Board Co. (Box 22)
  - Nye Schneider Fower Co. (Box 22)
  - Oakdale Grain Co. (Box 22)
  - Oats & Grain (Box 22)
  - J. B. Okie (Box 22)
  - J. B. Okie, Jr. (Box 22)
  - J. B. Okie, Jr. also Jimmie Okie (Box 22)
  - Van Okie and Howard Okie (Box 22)
  - Omaha Printing Co. (Box 22)
  - Omaha Stove - Repair Works (Box 22)
  - Omaha Tent & Awning Co. (Box 22)
  - Onken Bros. & West Co. (Box 22)
  - Orders re Mail (Box 22)
  - Oregon City Mfg. Co. (Box 22)
  - Millar Osborn Spice Co. (Box 22)
  - Owl Creek Coal Co. (Box 22)
  - Palmer Candy Co. (Box 23)
  - R. A. Patterson Tobacco Co. (Box 23)
  - Mr. John H. Paul (Box 23)
  - Paxton and Gallagher Co. (Box 23)
  - Jones Perpetual Ledger Co. (Box 23)
  - Peters Branch of International Shoe Co. (Box 23)
  - Phenix Ins. Co. (Box 23)
  - The Pierce Milling Co. (Box 23)
  - Pioneer Town Site Co. (Box 23)
  - J. E. Plummer Agent C. & N. W. Ry (Box 23)
  - Post Office Dept. (Box 23)
  - Geo W. Prior Hat Co. (Box 23)
  - Rasenbaum Bros. & Co. (Box 24)
  - J. E. Rate (Box 24)
  - Chas. Reck (Box 24)
  - Red Bank Telephone Co. (Box 24)
  - Register & Receiver (Box 24)
  - Frank O. Reid (Box 24)
  - Reid, Murdogh & Co. (Box 24)
  - Rhodes Ranch Egg Co. (Box 24)
  - Richards Ranch Drug Co. (Box 24)
  - Richardson Drug Co. (Box 24)
  - S. A. Rider Jewelry Co. (Box 24)
  - Ridger Ericson Engine Co. (Box 25)
  - Ripon Knitting Works (Box 25)
  - Roads Correspondence re: Road (Box 25)
  - Rocky Mountian Bell Telephone Co. (Box 25)
  - E. V. Roddin & Co. (Box 25)
  - Frank Russell Glove Co. (Box 25)
  - Russia Fur & Farming Co. (Box 25)
  - D. Sachs & Sons (Box 25)
  - Schlitz Brewing Co. (Box 25)
  - Mrs. And Mr. Dave Schoening (Box 25)
  - Schulte Hdw. Co. (Box 25)
  - V. V. Scoggan (Box 25)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Co. (Box 25)
  - Albert Sechrish Mfg. Co. (Box 25)
  - The George Sell Baking Co. (Box 25)
  - Sheehan & Fisher (Box 25)
  - Sheep (Box 26)
  - Shoshoni Capital Gazette (Box 26)
  - Shoshoni Commercial Co. (Box 26)
  - Shoshoni Creamery (Box 26)
  - Shoshoni Lumber Co. (Box 27)
  - Silberman Brothers (Box 27)
  - Sligo Iron Store Co. (Box 27)
  - M. E. Smith & Co. (Box 27)
  - Smith Motor Car Co. (Box 27)
  - G. Sommers & Co. (Box 27)
  - Stephenson Underwear Mills (Box 27)
  - John. B. Stetson Co. (Box 27)
  - Stone Ordean Wells Co. (Box 27)
  - Edward E. Strauss & Co. (Box 27)
  - Strauss Bros. (Box 27)
  - Struby-Estabrook Mercantile Co. (Box 28)
  - Studebaker Bros. Mfg. Co. (Box 28)
  - Studebaker Colorado Vehicle Co. (Box 28)
  - Otto Stumpf & Co. (Box 28)
  - W. E. Sullivan (Box 28)
  - The Surburg Co. (Box 28)
  - E. G. Swaim (Box 28)
  - Swift & Co. (Box 28)
  - Swift & Co. Denver, Colorado (Box 28)
  - R. D. Swisner Mfg. Co. (Box 28)
  - "T", 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - H. H. Tammen Curio Co., 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - G. L. Thorp & Co., 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - Toltec Oil Co., 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - Tome Athletic Store., 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - Tootle Wheeler & Matter Merc. Co., 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - Torpin Grain Co., 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - Trans-Mississippi Grain Co., 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - U-Y, 1919-1920 (Box 29)
  - U. S. Supply Co. (Box 29)
  - Updike Lumber & Coal Co. Hudson, Wyoming (Box 29)
  - Valentine Co. (Box 29)
  - "W", 1919-1920 (Box 30)
  - Walker Bin Co. (Box 30)
  - Washakie Trading Co. (Box 30)
  - Washburn - Crosby Co. (Box 30)
  - Chas. and Lucy Wells (Box 30)
  - Western Electrical Co. (Box 30)
  - Western Fruit Co. (Box 30)
  - The Western Steel Headgate Co. (Box 30)
  - Western Union (Box 30)
  - Western Union Telegraph Co. (Box 30)
  - Wheeler, Osgood & Co. (Box 30)
  - Wheeler and Matter Merc. Co. (Box 30)
  - The White Clover Butter Co. (Box 31)
  - Winchester Repeating Arms Co. (Box 31)
  - Winona Wagon Co. (Box 31)
  - Woodward & Lathrop (Box 31)
  - Mr. and Mrs. George Woolf (Box 31)
  - Worland Merc. Co. (Box 31)
  - Mrs. P. A. Wright (Box 31)
  - Wright & Wilhemy (Box 31)
  - Wyman, Pattridge & Co. (Box 31)
  - The Wyoming National Bank (Box 31)
  - Yellowstone Creamery (Box 31)
  - Zittlosen Mfg. Co. (Box 31)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - undated (Box 32)
  - 1894-1903 (Box 32)
  - 1904 January - September (Box 32)
  - 1904 October - December (Box 32)
  - 1905 January - May (Box 32)
  - 1905 June - September (Box 33)
  - 1905 October - December (Box 33)
  - 1906 January - August (Box 33)
  - 1906 September - December (Box 33)
  - 1907 January - August (Box 33)
  - 1907 September - December (Box 33)
  - 1908 January - March (Box 34)
  - 1908 April - May (Box 34)
  - 1908 June (Box 34)
  - 1908 July - August (Box 34)
  - 1908 September (Box 34)
  - 1908 October (Box 34)
  - 1908 November (Box 34)
  - 1908 December (Box 34)
  - 1909 January (Box 35)
  - 1909 February (Box 35)
  - 1909 March (Box 35)
  - 1909 April (Box 35)
  - 1909 May (Box 35)
  - 1909 June (Box 36)
  - 1909 July (Box 36)
  - 1909 August (Box 36)
  - 1909 September (Box 36)
  - 1909 October (Box 36)
  - 1909 November (Box 37)
  - 1909 December (Box 37)
  - 1910 January - February (Box 37)
  - 1910 March - April (Box 37)
  - 1910 May (Box 37)
  - 1910 June - July (Box 37)
  - 1910 August - September (Box 37)
  - 1910 October - November (Box 37)
  - 1910 December (Box 37)
  - 1911 January - February (Box 38)
  - 1911 March - April (Box 38)
  - 1911 May (Box 38)
  - 1911 June - July (Box 38)
  - 1911 August - September (Box 38)
  - 1911 October - November (Box 39)
  - 1911 December (Box 39)
  - 1911 January - March (Box 39)
  - 1912 April - June (Box 39)
  - 1912 July - September (Box 39)
  - 1912 October - December (Box 40)
  - 1913 January - February (Box 40)
  - 1913 March (Box 40)
  - 1913 April - May (Box 40)
  - 1913 June - July (Box 40)
  - 1913 August - September (Box 40)
  - 1913 October - December (Box 41)
  - 1914 January - February (Box 41)
  - 1914 March - April (Box 41)
  - 1914 May (Box 42)
  - 1914 June (Box 42)
  - 1914 July (Box 42)
  - 1914 August (Box 42)
  - 1914 September (Box 43)
  - 1914 October (Box 43)
  - 1914 November (Box 43)
  - 1914 December (Box 43)
  - 1915 January (Box 44)
  - 1915 February (Box 44)
  - 1915 March (Box 44)
  - 1915 April (Box 44)
  - 1915 May (Box 45)
  - 1915 June (Box 45)
  - 1915 July (Box 45)
  - 1915 August (Box 46)
  - 1915 September (Box 46)
  - 1915 October (Box 46)
  - 1915 November (Box 47)
  - 1915 December (Box 47)
  - 1916 January (Box 47)
  - 1916 February (Box 47)
  - 1916 March (Box 47)
  - 1916 April (Box 47)
  - 1916 May (Box 48)
  - 1916 June (Box 48)
  - 1916 July (Box 48)
  - 1916 August (Box 48)
  - 1916 September (Box 48)
  - 1916 October (Box 48)
  - 1916 November (Box 49)
  - 1916 December (Box 49)
  - 1917 January - April (Box 49)
  - 1917 May - December (Box 49)
  - 1919 May - June (Box 50)
  - 1919 July - September (Box 50)
  - 1919 October - December (Box 50)
  - 1920 January - April (Box 50)
  - 1920 May - July (Box 50)
  - 1921 January - December (Box 51)
- Series IV. Biographical Material, Manuscripts, and Notes
  - "In Memory of John B. Okie", Written and Read by Percy H. Shallenberger at Mr. Okie's Funeral. Mr. Okie Died November 5, 1930, Mimeographed (Box 51)
  - John Brognard Okie, Excerpt from National Cyclopedia Of American Biography, Volume XVII, Mimeographed Copy (Box 51)
  - Manuscript About the Okie Family (V. G. Okie) (Box 51)
  - Manuscript - 12 pages (Box 51)
  - Manuscript - 30 pages (Box 51)
  - Holograph Notes - 3 Pages of Notes, probably 1890s (Box 51)
- Series V. Account Records
  - The Bighorn Sheep Co. General Merchandise, Lost Cabin, Wyoming. 178 Tickets for Charge Accounts, Received by Mrs. Love from Valintino Baima, Nevada City, California (Box 51)
  - The Bighorn Sheep Co. General Merchandise, Lost Cabin, Wyoming. 72 Mailorder receipts, Received by Mrs. Love from Valintino Baima, Nevada City, California (Box 51)
  - The Bighorn Sheep Co. General Merchandise, Lost Cabin, Wyoming. 19 Receipt Book Total Sheets, Received by Mrs. Love from Valintino Baima, Nevada City, California (Box 51)
  - The Bighorn Sheep Co. General Merchandise, Lost Cabin, Wyoming. 4 Miscellaneous Pieces, Received by Mrs. Love from Valintino Baima, Nevada City, California (Box 51)